The Yale School of Music D.M.A. Papers
Yale University Music Library
The Yale School of Music D.M.A. Papers
1973-1997
MSS 13
Yale University Music Library
96
(176 boxes)
Dossiers documenting the professional activities of successful candidates for the degree of Doctor of Musical Arts in the Yale School of Music
Yale School of Music
Conditions Governing Access
Dossiers are made available for research in the Music Library upon application to a Music Library staff member. In some instances, permission to access an individual dossier may also require permission from the subject. Because the correspondence files contain confidential academic evaluations, they will remain sealed until 75 years after the D.M.A. was awarded.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically by year of degree.
Scope and Contents
The Yale School of Music D.M.A. Papers document the professional activities of successful candidates for the degree of Doctor of Musical Arts. The Papers cover a degree candidate's activities between receipt of the Master of Musical Arts degree and return for the D.M.A. degree. Included in the Papers are scrapbooks, correspondence, programs, reviews, sound recordings, and printed books and musical scores.
Biographical / Historical
The Doctor of Musical Arts degree program of the Yale School of Music was approved in 1968; the first degrees were awarded in 1973. As a prerequisite, candidates must have received the Master of Musical Arts degree from Yale, and then spend three to five years demonstrating their qualifications through distinguished achievement in their profession. Upon applying for the D.M.A. degree, the candidates submit a dossier of evidence demonstrating their professional competence and accomplishments. This evidence may include programs, brochures, reviews, compositions, recordings, publications, and other materials. Candidates are also required to give a recital and undergo an oral examination. Each year, the School of Music sends dossiers from successful candidates to the Library to become part of the D.M.A. Papers.
Conservatories of music -- United States; Music -- Instruction and study -- United States
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1973
  - Anderson, Marion - organ (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2048) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Burnham, Ann M. Woodward - viola (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2048) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Parisot, Elizabeth Sawyer - piano (Box 2)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2048) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1974
  - Lieberman, Carol - violin (Box 2)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2049) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Panetti, Joan - piano, composition (Box 2)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2049), programs, and reviews (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Thimmig, Leslie - composition (Box 3)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2049) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Tape (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Tape (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tape (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1975
  - Alstadter, Judith - piano (Box 4)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Green, Richard - trumpet (Box 4)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Record (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - House, C. Lawrence - trumpet (Box 4)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Keller, Janet Thom - piano (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Teaching material (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Killmer, Richard - oboe (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - More, Bruce - voice (Box 7)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Record (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tape (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tape (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Portney, Arlene - piano (Box 7)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050), programs, and reviews (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Ross, Barry - violin (Box 7)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Rozsynai, Imre - clarinet (Box 8)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050), programs, and reviews (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Spratlan, Melinda Kessler - voice (Box 8)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050), programs, and reviews (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Timm, Joel - oboe (Box 8)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Record (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vogel, Allan - oboe (Box 9)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wich, William - trumpet (Box 9)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2050) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1976
  - Bennett, Frank - composition (Box 10)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2051) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Compositions (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Compositions (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Tape (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Tape (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - deSilva, Preethi - harpsichord (Box 10)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2051) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Grice, Paul - clarinet (Box 10)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2051) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Grignet, Patricia - oboe (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2051) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Record (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Record (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Record (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Record (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Tape (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Parke, Richard - voice (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2051) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Tape (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Tape (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1977
  - Westney, William - piano (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2051 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Consoli, Marc-Antonio - composition (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2052) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Tape (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Tape (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - compositions (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - compositions (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mizelle, Diana - bass (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2052) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Noon, David - composition (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2052) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Tape (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Tape (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Compositions (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Compositions (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Tape (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1978
  - Borror, Ronald - trombone (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 13A, Folder 1)
  - Hennigan, Jack - organ (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Tape (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hobson, Ian - piano (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, James - organ (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Luby, Richard - violin (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Luti, Vincent - composition (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Tape (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Tape (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Tape (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Tape (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Tape (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Compositions (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - compositions (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Northington, David - piano (Box 14)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 13A, Folder 2)
  - Steen, Richard - voice (Box 14)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Stepner, Daniel - violin (Box 14)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2053) (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1979
  - Baldwin, David - trumpet (Box 15)
    - Transcriptions (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Compositions (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Recording (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Programs (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Transcriptions (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Transcriptions (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Tapes (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Borschel, Michael - clarinet (Box 16)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Programs (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Reviews (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Creider, Barbara - viola (Box 17)
    - Programs (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Reviews (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Crutcher, Ronald - cello (Box 17)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Programs (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Reviews (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cuckson, Robert - composition (Box 18)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Compositions (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Programs (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Macchia, Salvatore - bass (Box 18)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Programs (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Notices (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mott, David - composition (Box 19)
    - Arrangements (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Reviews (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Programs (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Compositions (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Tapes (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Nachman, Myrna - piano (Box 20)
    - Programs (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Reviews (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Publications (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sloane, Ethan - clarinet (Box 21)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Reviews (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Programs (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Smart, Gary Lee - composition (Box 21)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Compositions (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Programs (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Reviews (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Sullivan, Tim - composition (Box 22)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2054) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Tapes (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Compositions (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1980
  - Armstrong, Peter - piano (Box 23)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Biscardi, Chester - composition (Box 28)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Compositions (Box 28A, Folder 1)
  - Cowan, Carole - violin (Box 25)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Escandón, Teresa - piano (Box 24)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Résumé (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Ralph - violin (Box 24)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Parkins, Robert - organ (Box 26)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Résumé (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Programs and reviews (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Articles (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Polisi, Joseph - bassoon (Box 26)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Porter, William - organ (Box 27)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Shaffer, Frank - percussion (Box 27)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Standaart, Peter - flute (Box 27)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Programs (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Brochures (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Teaching Material (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Vukovic-Gay, Ilona - viola (Box 28)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2055) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Programs (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Tape (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Arrangements (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1981
  - Brody, Martin - composition (Box 29)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2056) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Scores (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Scores and tape (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Roberts, John Noel - piano (Box 29)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2056) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, Thomas - piano (Box 30)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2056) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Singleton, Kenneth - tuba (Box 30)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2056) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 1980-81 update (additional scrapbook) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Timm, Larry M. - oboe (Box 31)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2056) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Two tapes of DMA recital 11/11/77 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook of reviews and performances (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 1974-present scrapbook (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Weirich, Robert - piano (Box 32)
    - DMA support document (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2056) (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1982
  - Butler, Kathleen - violin (Box 33)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Carroll, Nansi - voice (Box 34)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, translation of Handel's Imeneo (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Résumé (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Compositions (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Cole, J. Roger - clarinet (Box 34)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Fagin, Gary - orchestral conducting (Box 35)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Compositions (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Duke Ellington big-band transcriptions (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Composition tapes: three cassettes, one reel (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Ims, Christine - viola (Box 36)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Marchant, Susan - organ (Box 38)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 38)
    - Scrapbook (Box 38)
    - Scrapbook (Box 38)
  - Mathews, William - composition (Box 38)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Compositions (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Phillips, Patricia McAwley - organ (Box 40)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Poses, Mary - flute (Box 40)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Showell, Jeffrey - 1982 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Swafford, Jan - composition (Box 41)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2057) (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - compositions (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1983
  - Brombaugh, Mark - organ (Box 41)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2058) (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Cox, Jeffrey - violin (Box 42)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2058) (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Composition by Peter Dickson Lopez, written for Jeffrey Cox (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Fisk, Charles B. - piano (Box 43)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2058) (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - MacKenzie, David - trombone (Box 43)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2058) (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Wilson, Carol - voice (Box 44)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2058) (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1984
  - Bowie, Lenard - trumpet (Box 45)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059), programs, newspaper articles (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Feliciano, Francisco F. - composition (Box 46)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Trio for soprano, viola, and clarinet (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper articles and programs (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Buk San Mo Ang Aming Maa Labi (score and tape) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - The Transfiggration (1983) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Excerpts from Yerma (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Program notes 1981 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Program notes 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook Jan.-Nov. 1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Four Asian Contemporary Composers (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Harvey, Raymond - orchestral conducting (Box 47)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Professional data: programs, recommendations (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Boyd M. - organ (Box 47)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Konzen, Richard - organ (Box 47)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Radzynski, Jan - composition (Box 48)
    - Scrapbook (Box 48)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Canto for solo piano (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Improvisazione for violoncello solo (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Sonata for violin solo (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Mizmorim for violin and 8 celli (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Tapes: Improvisazione and Kaddish (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Tapes: Canto and Stravinsky/Mendelssohn (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Urwin, Ray - organ (Box 49)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2059), programs, newspaper articles (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1985
  - Denza, William - clarinet (Box 50)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Garritson, Marie - flute (Box 51)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Jamison, Ward - conducting (Box 52)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Tape of performances (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Summary of Professional Activities, 4 c. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Lantz, Jere - orchestral conducting (Box 54)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Ling, Jahja - orchestral conducting (Box 55)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Marshall, Peter - organ (Box 56)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Murray, Bruce - piano (Box 56)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Overholt, Sheryl - voice (Box 57)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Perry, Timothy - orchestral conducting (Box 58)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Sound recording (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Rapp, Stephen - organ (Box 59)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Wynkoop, Rodney - choral conducting (Box 60)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2060) (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Tape (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1986
  - Beaser, Robert - composition (Box 61)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2061) (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Videotape (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Cassette tape (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - The Seven Deadly Sins (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Variations for Flute and Piano (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Il Est Né. Le Divin Enfant (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Note On A Southern Sky (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Mountain Songs (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Psalm 119 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Scenes From The Occasions (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Blaustein, Susan - composition (Box 63)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2061) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Cassette tape (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - To Orpheus: Four Sonnets (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Sextet (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Fantasie For Piano (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Ricercate (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Romansa: La Esposa de Don Garcia (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Song of Songs (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Concerto For Cello And Chamber Orchestra (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Goldray, Martin - piano (Box 61)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2061) (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Lalli, Richard (Box 65)
    - Scrapbook (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Roberts, Kay George - orchestral conducting (Box 66)
    - Scrapbook (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Doctor of Musical Arts Degree - 1987
  - Adkins, Elisabeth - violin (Box 66)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Robert Hart - orchestral conducting (Box 67)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbooks and Programs (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Ferlendis, G. Sonata for English Horn (Box 67, Folder 3)
      General
      Score edited by Baker
    - Bach, J.C. Quartet in G Major (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Daugherty, Michael K. - composition (Box 68)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Supplement to Scrapbooks (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Cassette Tape (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Celestial Hoops I & II (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Eurhythmic Toccata (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Piano Plus (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Beams Under The Action Of A Moving Rhythm (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Future Funk (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Miles In The Sky (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Walking Before Midnight (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Blaze Across The Sky (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Malvern, Gary Jay - trumpet (Box 70)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Supplement to Scrapbooks (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Parr, Andre Jon - piano (Box 71)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Schipull, Larry D. - organ (Box 72)
    - Correspondence (sealed until 2062) (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Swansbourne, Clive - piano (Box 72)